Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Whose Secret=
=سر من=
=Episode 9= (Wujian's Punishment)
=الحلقة 9= (عقاب ووجيان)
- Chief Inspector!
- المفتش العام!
Mr. Li,
السيد لي،
I have a few questions for you.
لدي بعض الأسئلة لك.
Mr. Li.
السيد لي.
Is it true that you shot Commander Jiang dead?
هل صحيح أنك قتلت القائد جيانغ بالرصاص؟
Mr. Li, please answer my question.
السيد لي، من فضلك أجب على سؤالي.
Mr. Li.
السيد لي.
Rumors say that you admire Miss Lu.
تقول الشائعات أنك معجب بالآنسة لو.
Your lust for her caused you to kill someone.
شهوتك لها تسببت في قتل شخص ما.
Do you have anything to explain to the people?
هل لديك أي شيء لتشرحه للناس؟
Everything you've heard is not true.
كل ما سمعته ليس صحيحا.
I hold responsibility for Killing Commander Jiang.
أنا أتحمل مسؤولية مقتل القائد جيانج.
It has nothing to do with other people.
ليس له علاقة بالآخرين.
I will give the public an explanation later.
سأقدم للجمهور توضيحا في وقت لاحق.
All of you are professional reporters.
أنتم جميعا صحفيين محترفين.
Thrusting someone into the spotlight
دفع شخص ما إلى دائرة الضوء
might not be too appropriate.
ربما لا يكون مناسبا للغاية.
If there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر،
please go back.
من فضلك عد إلى الوراء.
Mr. Li, say something.
السيد لي، قل شيئا.
Is this true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Wait for me at home.
انتظرني في المنزل.
I will deal with this.
سأتعامل مع هذا.
Send Miss Lu back.
أرسل الآنسة لو مرة أخرى.
Yes.
نعم.
Mr. Li, are the rumors true?
السيد لي، هل الشائعات صحيحة؟
Mr. Li, answer me.
السيد لي، أجبني.
Mr. Li, please answer my question.
السيد لي، من فضلك أجب على سؤالي.
Mr. Li!
السيد لي!
Boss,
رئيس،
you killed someone in the Mortal Realm for her.
لقد قتلت شخصًا في عالم البشر من أجلها.
I have a bad feeling about it.
لدي شعور سيء حول هذا الموضوع.
This is bad.
هذا سيء.
The Supreme Priest has come to the Mortal Realm.
لقد جاء الكاهن الأعظم إلى عالم البشر.
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
You broke the Wujian Rules because of Lu Huayan
لقد خرقت قواعد Wujian بسبب Lu Huayan
and got struck by lightning.
وضربتني صاعقة.
Is this even worth it?
هل يستحق هذا الأمر حقًا؟
It is.
إنها.
We meet again, Miss Lu.
لقد التقينا مرة أخرى، آنسة لو.
Mr. Jing,
السيد جينغ،
you keep trespassing on my house time and again.
تستمر في التعدي على منزلي مرارًا وتكرارًا.
Why are you doing this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
Of course, it's for your Mei pearl.
بالطبع، إنه من أجل لؤلؤة مي الخاصة بك.
Mei pearl?
مع اللؤلؤ؟
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
I think
أظن
I'll kill you first!
سأقتلك أولا!
He even gave you a gun.
حتى أنه أعطاك مسدسًا.
How loyal.
كم هي مخلصة.
What are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Li Motong will die without Mei pearl.
لي موتونغ سوف يموت بدون لؤلؤة مي.
You are just a petri dish for the Mei pearl
أنت مجرد طبق بتري للؤلؤة مي
yet you keep putting him in danger.
ومع ذلك فأنت تستمر في تعريضه للخطر.
You are an evil woman.
أنت امرأة شريرة.
You were trying to kill me a few days ago.
لقد كنت تحاول قتلي منذ بضعة أيام.
Your words cannot be trusted.
لا يمكن الوثوق بكلامك.
You don't believe me?
هل أنت لا تصدقني؟
Li Motong killed Jiang Mingfeng.
قتل لي موتونغ جيانغ مينجفنغ.
He is now being punished at Wujian.
يتم معاقبته الآن في Wujian.
Do you want to see it?
هل تريد رؤيته؟
He's being punished?
هل يتم معاقبته؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
You want to see it?
هل تريد رؤيته؟
I'll bring you there.
سأحضرك إلى هناك.
Li Motong!
لي موتونغ!
Yan.
نعم.
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
Jing Haisi, why did you bring her here?
جينغ هايسي، لماذا أحضرتها إلى هنا؟
Li Motong!
لي موتونغ!
Take her away!
خذها بعيدا!
Look at the disaster you bring.
انظر إلى الكارثة التي جلبتها.
Do you see how much suffering you've caused him?
هل ترى مقدار المعاناة التي سببتها له؟
Yan, leave.
يان، إذهب.
Yan!
الذي - التي!
How can all of you be so cruel?
كيف يمكنكم جميعا أن تكونوا قاسيين إلى هذه الدرجة؟
Let him go!
دعوه يذهب!
Aren't you quite capable?
هل أنت غير قادر تماما؟
Save him yourself.
أنقذه بنفسك.
Yan, leave now!
يان، إذهب الآن!
He has endured so much pain for you.
لقد تحمل الكثير من الألم من أجلك.
He even kneeled to me
حتى أنه ركع لي
for your soul.
من اجل روحك.
Without your Mei pearl,
بدون لؤلؤة مي الخاصة بك،
he will die soon.
سوف يموت قريبا.
I'm the one being punished,
أنا من يتم معاقبته
not him.
ليس هو.
Jing Haisi, let go of him.
جينغ هايسي، دعه يذهب.
I'm willing to be punished on his behalf.
أنا على استعداد لأن أعاقب نيابة عنه.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Kneel down, then.
اركع إذن.
Beg me.
توسل إلي.
Jing Haisi, you...
جينغ هايسي، أنت...
Don't listen to him.
لا تستمع إليه
No.
لا.
No, Yan!
لا، يان!
Don't kneel to him, Yan!
لا تركع له يا يان!
I beg you.
أرجوك.
Please save him.
من فضلك انقذه.
How sincere.
كم هو صادق.
I beg you.
أرجوك.
Please save him!
من فضلك انقذه!
However, you kneeled for nothing.
لكنك ركعت من أجل لا شيء.
I was just fooling around with you.
لقد كنت أمزح معك فقط.
What must I do for you to let go of Yan?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل حتى أتركك يان؟
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
I won't take her away.
لن آخذها بعيدا.
I'm going to let her be punished together with you.
سأتركها تعاقب معك.
I won't kill her.
لن أقتلها
However, I have thousands of ways to torture her.
لكن لدي آلاف الطرق لتعذيبها.
Humans are lowly.
البشر متواضعون.
She is just a vessel for the Mei pearl.
إنها مجرد وعاء للؤلؤة مي.
Death is her only fate.
الموت هو مصيرها الوحيد
I've told you
لقد قلت لك
that the Mei pearl is my matter alone.
أن لؤلؤة مي هي ملكي وحدي.
I don't need you to interfere.
لا أحتاج إلى تدخلك.
Jing Haisi,
جينغ هايسي،
I order you as the Lord of Wujian
أنا آمرك باعتبارك سيد ووجيان
to get out of Wujian
للخروج من ووجيان
and never come back.
ولا تعود أبدًا.
As expected of my younger brother.
كما هو متوقع من أخي الأصغر.
You are the Lord of Wujian indeed.
أنت سيد Wujian بالفعل.
This is not over between us yet.
هذا لم ينتهي بيننا بعد.
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
For you,
لك،
everything I do is worth it.
كل ما أفعله يستحق ذلك.
Thank you,
شكرًا لك،
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
♪The evil spirit's hand pushes her♪
♪يد الروح الشريرة تدفعها♪
♪Into a kiss upon the rail♪
♪في قبلة على السكة♪
♪Where does the truth pretend to sleep?♪
♪أين تتظاهر الحقيقة بالنوم؟♪
♪Perfect last words confront what cannot be faced♪
♪الكلمات الأخيرة المثالية تواجه ما لا يمكن مواجهته♪
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
As the Lord of Wujian,
بصفتي سيد ووجيان،
how could they be so cruel to you?
كيف يمكن أن يكونوا قاسيين معك إلى هذه الدرجة؟
♪Whispering their filthy confession♪
♪همس اعترافهم القذر♪
Wujian has its own rules.
Wujian لديه قواعده الخاصة.
♪A white cat intently licks the thick sweet scent of blood♪
♪قطة بيضاء تلعق باهتمام رائحة الدم الحلوة الكثيفة♪
Are you concerned about me?
هل أنت قلق علي؟
Jing Haisi told me
أخبرني جينغ هايسي
that if you insist on not taking the Mei pearl,
إذا كنت تصر على عدم أخذ لؤلؤة مي،
you will really die.
سوف تموت حقا.
Is it true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I am the Lord of Wujian.
أنا سيد ووجيان.
Not taking a Mei pearl
عدم أخذ لؤلؤة مي
won't kill me.
لن تقتلني
But you...
ولكنك...
You kneeled to Jing Haisi
لقد ركعت أمام جينغ هايسي
to get my soul back.
لاستعادة روحي.
You also killed a human to protect me
لقد قتلت إنسانًا أيضًا لحمايتي
and ended up being struck by lightning.
وإنتهى به الأمر إلى أن أصيب بصاعقة.
Why do you treat me so well?
لماذا تعاملني بهذه الطريقة الجيدة؟
Have you forgotten our wedding in the church?
هل نسيت حفل زفافنا في الكنيسة؟
It might be fake for you
ربما يكون مزيفًا بالنسبة لك
but it is real
لكنها حقيقية
for me.
لي.
You are more important than my life.
أنت أكثر أهمية من حياتي.
Nothing is more important than your life.
لا يوجد شيء أكثر أهمية من حياتك.
Your sister died because of Wujian's demon beasts.
لقد ماتت أختك بسبب وحوش شيطان ووجيان.
I'm worried that you might hate Wujian or me.
أنا قلق من أنك قد تكره Wujian أو تكرهني.
So, you must stay close to me.
لذلك، يجب عليك البقاء بالقرب مني.
You are right.
أنت محق.
Evil isn't the only thing in Wujian.
الشر ليس الشيء الوحيد في Wujian.
You've brought me redemption
لقد جلبت لي الفداء
instead of massacre.
بدلا من المذبحة.
♪Who are you, who am I?♪
♪من أنت، من أنا؟♪
♪How did everything turn against itself?♪
♪كيف انقلب كل شيء ضد نفسه؟♪
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
(You got hurt all over for me.)
(لقد تأذيت في كل مكان من أجلي.)
(You were not afraid of death.)
(لم تكن خائفا من الموت.)
(You taught me the difference between good and evil)
(علمتني الفرق بين الخير والشر)
(and let go of the knot in my heart.)
(وأطلق العنان للعقدة التي في قلبي).
(Li Motong,)
(لي موتونج،)
(your love)
(حبك)
(made me fall for you.)
(جعلني أقع في حبك.)
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
♪Her long hair with the dark night♪
♪شعرها الطويل مع الليل المظلم♪
♪Looks so pure in the lamplight♪
♪يبدو نقيًا جدًا في ضوء المصباح♪
♪Blurred flesh and tears♪
♪لحم مشوش ودموع♪
♪The evil spirit's hand pushes her into a kiss upon the rail♪
♪يد الروح الشريرة تدفعها إلى قبلة على السور♪
♪Where does the truth pretend to sleep?♪
♪أين تتظاهر الحقيقة بالنوم؟♪
♪Perfect last words confront what cannot be faced♪
♪الكلمات الأخيرة المثالية تواجه ما لا يمكن مواجهته♪
♪The scent corroded by the dawn♪
♪الرائحة المتآكلة بالفجر♪
♪Is her hollow soul tossed within a bottle♪
♪هل روحها المجوفة ملقاة داخل زجاجة♪
♪Bloodless lips bloom into bright petals♪
♪شفاه بلا دم تتفتح في بتلات مشرقة♪
♪Whispering their filthy confession♪
♪همس اعترافهم القذر♪
♪A white cat intently licks the thick sweet scent of blood♪
♪قطة بيضاء تلعق باهتمام رائحة الدم الحلوة الكثيفة♪
♪Accusing, demanding♪
♪متهم، متطلب♪
♪Who are you, who am I?♪
♪من أنت، من أنا؟♪
♪How did everything turn against itself?♪
♪كيف انقلب كل شيء ضد نفسه؟♪
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
♪The restless bones beneath♪
♪العظام المضطربة في الأسفل♪
♪To which gravestone point her broken fingers♪
♪إلى أي شاهد قبر تشير أصابعها المكسورة♪
♪Who trembles, who grieves?♪
♪من يرتجف، من يحزن؟♪
♪Who is guiltless, who bears sin?♪
♪من هو البريء، من يتحمل الخطيئة؟♪
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
♪He kisses her fingertips♪
♪يقبل أطراف أصابعها♪
♪Bare joints blooming white iris♪
♪المفاصل العارية تتفتح زهور السوسن البيضاء♪
♪Nightmares and roses lie asleep♪
♪الكوابيس والورود نائمة♪
♪Nothing but a date with death♪
♪لا شيء سوى موعد مع الموت♪